One night can cost you everything.
Knock Knock is a horror, thriller film directed by Eli Roth.
When a devoted husband and father is left home alone for the weekend, two
stranded young women unexpectedly knock on his door for help.
What starts out as a kind gesture results in a dangerous
seduction and a deadly game of cat and mouse.
Evan Webber, played by Keanu Reeves.
Genesis, played by Lorenza Izzo.
Bel, played by Ana de Armas.
Louis, played by Aaron Burns.
Vivian, played by Colleen Camp.
Karen Alvarado, played by Ignacia Allamand.
Knock Knock is a 2015 thriller film directed by Eli Roth, who also
co-wrote the script with Guillermo Amoedo and Nicolás López.
The film stars Keanu Reeves, Lorenza Izzo and Ana de Armas.
The film was released on October 9, 2015, by Lionsgate Premiere.
Knock Knock is a remake of Death Game (shot in 1974, not
released until 1977), which was directed by Peter S.
Traynor and starred Sondra Locke and Colleen Camp.
All three individuals had a hand in the production of Knock
Knock, while Camp also had a cameo in the newer film.
The film explores themes of adultery, infidelity, sadism, cake, disc jockey.
The tone is dark and intense.